1
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
{\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕

2
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:05,000
{\pos(235.108,242)}最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利

3
00:00:06,510 --> 00:00:11,510
{\an4}{\pos(35,235)}翻译     累

4
00:00:11,510 --> 00:00:16,510
{\an4}{\pos(35,235)}校对     累

5
00:00:16,510 --> 00:00:21,510
{\an4}{\pos(27,235)}时间轴     西·查

6
00:00:21,510 --> 00:00:26,510
{\an4}{\pos(35,235)}后期     累

7
00:00:26,510 --> 00:00:31,510
{\an4}{\pos(35,235)}总监     累

8
00:00:45,150 --> 00:00:46,880
我睡过头了
I overslept.

9
00:00:49,190 --> 00:00:50,420
是啊  你
Yeah, well... you...

10
00:00:51,690 --> 00:00:53,800
你睡了就好
You slept. That's what matters.

11
00:00:54,610 --> 00:00:56,600
现在去钓鱼是不是太晚了
Is it too late to go fishing now?

12
00:01:00,370 --> 00:01:03,650
鳟鱼很像银行家
Trout are like... they're like bankers.

13
00:01:04,160 --> 00:01:06,270
它们早上什么都不做
They don't do a damn thing in the morning.

14
00:01:10,000 --> 00:01:11,200
我能尝尝吗
Can I try some?

15
00:01:11,460 --> 00:01:13,410
不行  这会阻碍你的成长
Nah. It'll stunt your growth.

16
00:01:13,800 --> 00:01:15,120
什么意思
What does that mean?

17
00:01:15,630 --> 00:01:17,160
意思是它会让你变矮
Means it'll make you short.

18
00:01:18,760 --> 00:01:20,290
我已经很矮了
I'm already short.

19
00:01:22,140 --> 00:01:25,750
你要是喝咖啡就不会这么矮了
Yeah, well, not as short as you'll be if you drink coffee.

20
00:01:26,640 --> 00:01:29,090
想钓大鱼  就带上渔网吧
Why don't you bring the net if you're planning on a big one.

21
00:01:31,230 --> 00:01:33,180
我们为什么不能住在这里
Why can't we live right here?

22
00:01:33,440 --> 00:01:36,300
一直这样生活
Like this. All the time.

23
00:01:37,860 --> 00:01:41,180
我每天也在问自己同样的问题  孙子
You know, I ask myself the same thing, grandson, every day.

24
00:01:42,830 --> 00:01:43,940
每天
Every day.

25
00:02:37,380 --> 00:02:40,840
{\an8}黄石
第三季  第二集

26
00:03:29,060 --> 00:03:30,460
你尝过炸面包吗
You ever had fry bread?

27
00:03:38,650 --> 00:03:41,010
小时候我妈经常给我做
My mother used to make it for me when I was young.

28
00:03:43,240 --> 00:03:44,180
咖啡
Coffee?

29
00:03:45,370 --> 00:03:46,230
谢谢
Thanks.

30
00:03:46,700 --> 00:03:48,240
步骤是
So, what you want to do is you...

31
00:03:48,240 --> 00:03:50,860
先把培根放进去
Take this bacon, put it down first.

32
00:03:52,080 --> 00:03:55,280
把鸡蛋放在上面
Take the eggs, put them over the top.

33
00:03:55,750 --> 00:03:56,820
这样
Like that.

34
00:04:05,720 --> 00:04:06,620
你饿了吗
You hungry?

35
00:04:08,680 --> 00:04:10,750
-嗯  -过来坐
- Yeah. - Come sit.

36
00:04:37,380 --> 00:04:38,530
你不吃吗
You're not eating?

37
00:04:39,880 --> 00:04:41,660
贝丝  我几小时前就吃了
Beth, I ate hours ago.

38
00:04:43,010 --> 00:04:44,240
我还是看着你吧
I think I'll just watch you.

39
00:05:03,110 --> 00:05:03,970
那就好
Good.

40
00:07:15,450 --> 00:07:17,350
你要去夏季露营吗
Hey, are you going up to the summer camp?

41
00:07:17,700 --> 00:07:19,870
是啊  把这些筐装满就去
Yeah, as soon as I get these panniers full.

42
00:07:19,870 --> 00:07:22,190
我能和你一起去吗  我想看看我儿子
Cool if I ride with you? I want to see my kid.

43
00:07:24,380 --> 00:07:26,950
莫妮卡  要是你摔下马  他们肯定会找我算账的
Monica, if you fall off, they're gonna have my ass.

44
00:07:27,260 --> 00:07:28,570
我不会摔下去的
I won't fall off.

45
00:07:29,050 --> 00:07:30,780
-万一你摔下马  -准备好了吗
- But if you do... - We ready?

46
00:07:34,720 --> 00:07:36,370
她想和我们一起去
She wants to ride up there with us.

47
00:07:37,270 --> 00:07:39,580
好吧  去给她找匹马
All right, well, go grab her a horse.

48
00:07:40,600 --> 00:07:42,270
好马都在营地
All the good ones are up at camp.

49
00:07:42,270 --> 00:07:44,770
这里只剩一堆歪瓜裂枣
The only thing left here is a bunch of freight trains and monsters.

50
00:07:44,770 --> 00:07:46,920
你的马怎么了吗  杰克
Well, what the fuck is wrong with your horse, Jake?

51
00:07:46,940 --> 00:07:48,230
这是我的马
Well, that's my horse.

52
00:07:48,230 --> 00:07:50,390
莫妮卡  骑杰克的马
Monica, get on Jake's horse.

53
00:07:50,950 --> 00:07:52,050
-走吧  -但是
- Come on. - But--

54
00:07:52,660 --> 00:07:53,990
没时间扯淡了
We don't have time for this shit.

55
00:07:53,990 --> 00:07:55,720
去拿匹马  快点
Just go get a horse. Let's go.

56
00:08:12,680 --> 00:08:14,470
他的马好像有点生气
His horse seems a bit angry.

57
00:08:14,470 --> 00:08:15,930
是啊  有一点
Yeah, a little bit.

58
00:08:21,680 --> 00:08:23,810
-他为什么选那匹马  -你知道吗  莫妮卡
- Why did he pick that one? - You know what, Monica?

59
00:08:23,810 --> 00:08:26,130
他的脑子可不算灵光的
He ain't the sharpest tool in the shed, let me tell you.

60
00:08:27,730 --> 00:08:30,130
我想要我的好马
Want my goddamn good horse back!

61
00:08:32,780 --> 00:08:34,200
这下有意思了
Oh, now that looks fun.

62
00:08:34,200 --> 00:08:36,560
莫妮卡  他好像不这么觉得
Monica, I don't think he's having too much fun.

63
00:08:38,660 --> 00:08:40,230
莫妮卡  靠
Hey Monica, goddamn it.

64
00:08:57,220 --> 00:08:59,120
那就无所谓了  不是吗
Well, it doesn't matter, then, does it?

65
00:09:00,390 --> 00:09:02,120
赶紧搞定  好吗
Just get it done, okay?

66
00:09:05,900 --> 00:09:07,730
干得漂亮
That's exactly how you do it.

67
00:09:07,730 --> 00:09:08,960
瞧瞧你
Look at you.

68
00:09:09,070 --> 00:09:10,730
甚至不需要炊事车
Don't even need a chuck wagon.

69
00:09:10,730 --> 00:09:11,860
我们需要柠檬
We need lemon.

70
00:09:11,860 --> 00:09:14,140
炊事车上有一大袋
There's a big bag of them on the wagon.

71
00:09:14,280 --> 00:09:15,260
我去拿
I'll get it.

72
00:09:16,610 --> 00:09:18,890
该死
Aye. Goddamn it.

73
00:09:19,950 --> 00:09:20,890
喂
Yeah?

74
00:09:23,200 --> 00:09:25,730
不  我没这么说
No. Not what I said.

75
00:09:26,580 --> 00:09:27,730
能听见吗
Can you hear me?

76
00:09:29,250 --> 00:09:30,210
喂
Hello?

77
00:09:30,210 --> 00:09:31,360
爷爷
Grandpa.

78
00:09:34,920 --> 00:09:36,200
一片还是两片
One slice or two?

79
00:09:37,550 --> 00:09:40,000
-两片吧  -好的
- I'd go two. - Okay.

80
00:09:43,520 --> 00:09:46,210
该死
Goddamn it.

81
00:09:47,810 --> 00:09:48,730
喂
Yeah.

82
00:09:48,730 --> 00:09:51,340
你到哪都有工作啊  爷爷
Work follows you wherever you go, grandpa.

83
00:09:52,360 --> 00:09:54,300
说的太对了
Truer words were never spoken.

84
00:09:54,900 --> 00:09:55,930
喂
Yeah?

85
00:09:58,610 --> 00:10:01,600
不  土地管理权出售时再转让
No, the BLM transfers with the sale,

86
00:10:01,950 --> 00:10:04,190
但他们必须重新申请  没错
but they have to reapply. That's right.

87
00:10:05,790 --> 00:10:06,770
喂
Hello?

88
00:10:08,580 --> 00:10:09,900
该死
Goddamn it.

89
00:10:21,390 --> 00:10:22,960
所有东西都搬上去
Everything moves up here.

90
00:10:23,600 --> 00:10:25,010
全都搬上去
I want everything up here.

91
00:10:25,020 --> 00:10:26,920
帐篷  篝火
The tents. The fire.

92
00:10:27,480 --> 00:10:29,380
所有的一切
The whole goddamn everything.

93
00:11:35,170 --> 00:11:36,740
这个营地更好吗
Is this a better camp?

94
00:11:38,710 --> 00:11:39,910
我看看
Let's see.

95
00:11:39,720 --> 00:11:41,550
{\an8}无法激活移动服务

96
00:11:41,510 --> 00:11:44,580
是的  这个营地好多了
Yep, this camp is much better.

97
00:11:53,350 --> 00:11:55,380
牲畜委员会  有什么可以帮您
Livestock Commission, how can I help you?

98
00:11:56,690 --> 00:11:58,320
稍等  我看看
Just one moment, let me check.

99
00:11:58,320 --> 00:12:00,150
-早上好  杰米  -早上好  海伦
- Morning, Jamie. - Good morning, Helen.

100
00:12:00,150 --> 00:12:01,780
甜草县检察官在一号线
Sweet Grass County attorney on line one.

101
00:12:01,780 --> 00:12:04,100
-要接过去吗  -好
- Put him through? - Sure.

102
00:12:25,850 --> 00:12:26,680
兰迪
Hey, Randy.

103
00:12:26,680 --> 00:12:29,250
你听说绕桶赛手器具被偷的事了吗
You hear about these barrel racers got their rigs stolen?

104
00:12:29,350 --> 00:12:30,210
没有
No.

105
00:12:30,350 --> 00:12:32,520
两个女孩在给马装器具
These two girls loaded up their horses,

106
00:12:32,520 --> 00:12:34,190
最后一次检查马厩时
were making one last check in the stalls,

107
00:12:34,190 --> 00:12:36,130
被几个人袭击了
and got jumped by a couple of guys.

108
00:12:36,150 --> 00:12:37,400
弄的挺惨
Worked 'em pretty good,

109
00:12:37,400 --> 00:12:39,940
把她们锁在马厩  开车跑了
locked em in a horse stall, drove off in their rigs.

110
00:12:39,940 --> 00:12:42,610
抢了她们的卡车  拖车  马  马鞍  所有东西
Took their trucks, trailers, horses, saddles, everything.

111
00:12:42,610 --> 00:12:43,890
我靠
Jesus.

112
00:12:44,030 --> 00:12:47,390
马被偷了  所以这事归你管
Since horses were stolen, sort of falls into your court, too.

113
00:12:47,660 --> 00:12:49,560
我缺人手
I'm short-handed on deputies.

114
00:12:50,200 --> 00:12:51,560
你能派个探员吗
Can you spare an agent?

115
00:12:51,830 --> 00:12:53,560
好  我给你派一个
Yeah, I'll send you one.

116
00:12:53,710 --> 00:12:56,650
如果我们处理得当  你能交到很多朋友
You can make a lot of friends if we handle this the right way.

117
00:13:00,710 --> 00:13:02,050
怎么叫得当
What's the right way?

118
00:13:02,050 --> 00:13:03,820
处理得当可以传递信息
The right way sends a message.

119
00:13:05,380 --> 00:13:06,490
你懂我的意思吗
You know what I mean?

120
00:13:09,140 --> 00:13:10,120
我懂
I know what you mean.

121
00:13:15,810 --> 00:13:19,590
海伦  能让亨顿探员来一趟办公室吗
Helen, could you have Agent Hendon come by the office, please?

122
00:13:33,500 --> 00:13:34,540
快看
Look.

123
00:13:34,540 --> 00:13:35,730
妈妈
Mama!

124
00:13:37,170 --> 00:13:39,740
小样  宝贝  玩得开心吗
Oh, look at you, baby. You having fun?

125
00:13:39,840 --> 00:13:40,990
开心
Yeah.

126
00:13:41,800 --> 00:13:44,280
这里就是钓鱼吃鱼  钓鱼吃鱼
All we do is fish and eat and fish and eat.

127
00:13:45,300 --> 00:13:47,340
这是医嘱吗
That's just what the doctor ordered, huh?

128
00:13:47,340 --> 00:13:49,180
是啊  没有更好的药了
Yeah. No better medicine.

129
00:13:49,180 --> 00:13:50,410
你爸呢
Where's your dad?

130
00:13:50,640 --> 00:13:52,010
寻找狼群
Looking for wolves.

131
00:13:52,010 --> 00:13:54,040
听起来不妙啊  他在哪
Well, that sounds ominous. Which way?

132
00:13:54,060 --> 00:13:55,380
应该在那边
Bet he's that way.

133
00:14:00,270 --> 00:14:02,220
这匹马居然驯服了  杰克
Didn't think that one was broke, Jake.

134
00:14:02,360 --> 00:14:04,890
今天过后它肯定是驯服了
By God, after a day like today he is.

135
00:14:05,320 --> 00:14:07,100
我看出来了
Yeah, I see that.

136
00:14:11,330 --> 00:14:12,680
我们以前就这么干
That's how we used to do it.

137
00:14:13,540 --> 00:14:17,110
是啊  应该延续下来的
Yeah, well, never should have stopped.

138
00:14:21,540 --> 00:14:24,240
先生  我想谢谢你来着
Well, sir, I wanted to... thank you.

139
00:14:25,380 --> 00:14:27,070
我只是一直没有
You know, I just haven't had, uh...

140
00:14:27,720 --> 00:14:28,910
找到机会
...been the right time.

141
00:14:29,220 --> 00:14:32,040
不用  那房子是你应得的  里普
No need. You deserve that house, Rip.

142
00:14:32,810 --> 00:14:34,160
不  先生  我
No, sir, I'm, uh...

143
00:14:34,310 --> 00:14:35,750
我说的是那封信
I'm talking about the letter.

144
00:14:37,810 --> 00:14:40,050
从来没有人给我写过这样的信
Nobody's ever given me anything like that before.

145
00:14:44,730 --> 00:14:47,190
既然我们今年夏天要在这里盯着
Anyways, if we're gonna staked out this summer,

146
00:14:47,190 --> 00:14:48,970
还是多找些牧人吧
we ought to get some more wranglers, you know?

147
00:14:49,610 --> 00:14:51,530
我们很快就会人手不足
We're gonna run out of hands pretty quick around here.

148
00:14:51,530 --> 00:14:53,490
你雇的那个女孩呢
What happened to that girl you hired?

149
00:14:53,490 --> 00:14:55,330
她是流浪者  来来去去的
She's a drifter. Drifters drift.

150
00:14:55,330 --> 00:14:56,480
你懂的
You know how it is.

151
00:14:56,580 --> 00:14:58,730
是啊  这样也好
Yeah. Probably for the best.

152
00:14:59,040 --> 00:15:02,820
工棚最好不要有女孩
Girl in the bunkhouse was a disaster waiting to happen.

153
00:15:03,250 --> 00:15:06,610
其实工棚还挺消停的
She actually, uh, she kept the bunkhouse pretty honest.

154
00:15:06,960 --> 00:15:08,780
-真的吗  -是的
- That a fact? - Yes, sir.

155
00:15:11,970 --> 00:15:15,460
交给你了  工棚归你管
I'll leave it to you. You run the bunkhouse.

156
00:15:19,230 --> 00:15:20,920
先生  凯斯知道吗
Sir, does Kayce know that?

157
00:15:21,270 --> 00:15:22,750
是凯斯的主意
It was Kayce's idea.

158
00:15:28,780 --> 00:15:30,640
找到人我会告诉你的
I'll let you know what I find.

159
00:15:32,200 --> 00:15:33,390
去吧
You do that.

160
00:15:38,120 --> 00:15:39,150
如果你
If you, uh...

161
00:15:39,910 --> 00:15:42,290
你再雇女孩的话  必须找刻薄或者丑的
you hire another girl, she needs to be mean or ugly.

162
00:15:42,290 --> 00:15:43,210
二选一
One of the two.

163
00:15:43,210 --> 00:15:45,900
我不希望有坠入爱河的牛仔
Last thing I need is some love-struck cowboy

164
00:15:46,340 --> 00:15:48,250
上错了床  明白吗
climbing in the wrong bunk, know what I mean?

165
00:15:48,260 --> 00:15:50,240
刻薄或者丑  遵命
Mean or ugly. Yes, sir.

166
00:16:12,400 --> 00:16:13,510
没事吧
Everything all right?

167
00:16:15,200 --> 00:16:18,270
家里没人
Well... There's no one at the house.

168
00:16:18,580 --> 00:16:20,020
谷仓也没人
No one at the barn.

169
00:16:20,870 --> 00:16:22,860
感觉有点孤单
Just feeling kinda lonely.

170
00:16:26,250 --> 00:16:27,280
孤单
Lonely, huh?

171
00:16:28,880 --> 00:16:29,780
是啊
Yeah.

172
00:16:30,130 --> 00:16:31,870
这可不行
Well, we can't have that.

173
00:16:32,260 --> 00:16:33,870
-肯定不行  -嗯
- Can't do that. - No.

174
00:17:00,040 --> 00:17:01,190
怎么办
What do we do?

175
00:17:05,420 --> 00:17:08,280
你这个倒霉孩子  现在出现了
You are one lucky son of a bitch, you show up now.

176
00:17:08,340 --> 00:17:09,740
宝贝  现在怎么办
Baby, what do we do?

177
00:17:14,050 --> 00:17:17,870
想看就让它看吧
If he wants to watch, we just let him watch.

178
00:17:45,710 --> 00:17:47,690
看  他睡着了
Look at him. He's sleeping.

179
00:17:49,540 --> 00:17:51,990
是啊
Yeah, I know.

180
00:17:52,380 --> 00:17:54,860
我以为他再也睡不着了
Oh, I never thought he'd sleep again.

181
00:17:57,050 --> 00:17:58,700
我也这么以为
I thought the same thing.

182
00:18:03,970 --> 00:18:06,460
每天都像这样就好了
I wish our lives were like this every day.

183
00:18:07,270 --> 00:18:08,630
就像这样
Just like this.

184
00:18:10,730 --> 00:18:11,880
可以啊
It can be.

185
00:18:12,520 --> 00:18:14,010
不  不行
No, it can't.

186
00:18:14,440 --> 00:18:15,840
已经成为过去了
Used to be.

187
00:18:17,700 --> 00:18:20,970
我们原来一百万年的生活方式
But now the way we used to live for a million years is...

188
00:18:22,660 --> 00:18:23,950
变成了一个活动
it's just an event.

189
00:18:23,950 --> 00:18:26,690
周末或假日的活动
Something we do on weekends or holidays.

190
00:18:29,290 --> 00:18:32,320
我每天都可以这样
I could do this every day of my life just like this.

191
00:18:34,210 --> 00:18:36,200
如果你想要这样的生活  就说出来
If that's what you want, just say it.

192
00:18:39,010 --> 00:18:40,330
这就是我想要的生活
That's what I want.

193
00:18:43,680 --> 00:18:44,660
好的
Okay.

194
00:18:46,230 --> 00:18:48,630
我保证会想办法帮你实现的
Then I promise I'll find a way to give it to you.

195
00:18:51,690 --> 00:18:54,130
我会耐心等待的
I'll find the patience to wait.

196
00:18:56,280 --> 00:18:57,840
这并不容易  你知道吗
It won't be easy, you know?

197
00:18:59,150 --> 00:19:00,850
你得放弃很多
You'll have to give up a lot.

198
00:19:01,280 --> 00:19:03,480
宝贝  和你在一起什么都不容易
Baby, nothing's easy with you.

199
00:19:05,540 --> 00:19:07,600
我已经放弃了我的一切
And I've given up everything I got.

200
00:19:16,090 --> 00:19:18,200
我就知道星星能帮到他
I knew the stars would help him.

201
00:20:18,070 --> 00:20:19,720
和你的狼群失散了吗
Lost your pack, huh?

202
00:20:23,700 --> 00:20:25,100
不知道该去哪里
Don't know where to go.

203
00:20:26,620 --> 00:20:28,230
你在找朋友
You're looking for friends.

204
00:20:38,300 --> 00:20:39,450
看着我
Look at me...

205
00:20:40,880 --> 00:20:42,870
我不是你的朋友
and know that I am not your friend.

206
00:20:44,970 --> 00:20:46,240
我是你的敌人
I'm your enemy.

207
00:20:48,390 --> 00:20:51,420
由不得你喜不喜欢
Whether I like it or not, I am.

208
00:20:53,190 --> 00:20:55,550
这里没什么值得你留恋的  好吗
There's nothing for you here, okay?

209
00:20:57,520 --> 00:21:00,050
你可以回归森林  但山谷是我的
I'll give you the forest, but the valley is mine.

210
00:21:02,150 --> 00:21:03,550
牛群是我的
The cattle are mine.

211
00:21:04,030 --> 00:21:07,680
如果你想夺走  我就杀了你
If you try to take them, I'll kill you.

212
00:21:28,640 --> 00:21:30,330
我父亲也可以
My father could do that...

213
00:21:32,140 --> 00:21:35,420
跟动物说话  它们也会听
...talk to animals and they'd listen.

214
00:21:36,310 --> 00:21:38,250
我都不知道它有没有在听
I'm not sure if he was listening.

215
00:21:39,650 --> 00:21:41,130
它在听  儿子
He was listening, son.

216
00:21:44,320 --> 00:21:45,550
抱歉吵醒你了
Sorry to wake you.

217
00:21:46,660 --> 00:21:47,970
你没吵醒我
You didn't wake me.

218
00:21:49,870 --> 00:21:50,980
你听到河水声了吗
You hear that river?

219
00:21:53,580 --> 00:21:55,730
地球上有七十亿人
There's seven billion people on the planet

220
00:21:56,330 --> 00:21:57,980
没人知道我在这里
not one of them know I'm here.

221
00:22:00,960 --> 00:22:02,070
一个人都没有
Not one.

222
00:22:02,750 --> 00:22:04,450
谁都不知道
Not a goddamn soul.

223
00:22:06,680 --> 00:22:07,700
晚安  爸
Good night, Dad.

224
00:22:08,930 --> 00:22:09,910
爱你
I love you.

225
00:22:23,240 --> 00:22:25,530
{\an8}舒瓦茨和梅耶公司

226
00:22:26,790 --> 00:22:28,980
他们买了你应该不奇怪吧
Shouldn't surprise you they bought it.

227
00:22:29,120 --> 00:22:30,210
要是我们买的就好了
Wish we'd bought it.

228
00:22:30,210 --> 00:22:32,440
我不奇怪他们买了
It doesn't surprise me they bought it.

229
00:22:32,460 --> 00:22:34,340
我奇怪的是他们居然知道
Surprises me they knew about it.

230
00:22:34,340 --> 00:22:38,320
这么大的公司想在这个山谷发展
I mean, if a company this big wants to develop in this valley,

231
00:22:38,670 --> 00:22:40,580
应该先找我们吧
we are the first call, right?

232
00:22:41,090 --> 00:22:42,130
但他们没找
But we weren't.

233
00:22:42,140 --> 00:22:44,640
现在纽约的律师大摇大摆地
And now I have New York attorneys swaggering

234
00:22:44,640 --> 00:22:46,290
走过我们的牧场
through our fucking fields.

235
00:22:46,310 --> 00:22:48,830
谁是市场股票的主要竞争对手
Who is Market Equities main competition?

236
00:22:50,230 --> 00:22:52,630
米高梅  万豪
MGM. Marriott.

237
00:22:53,440 --> 00:22:55,840
万豪有什么是他们没有的
What does Marriott own that they don't?

238
00:22:58,990 --> 00:23:00,100
滑雪场
Ski resort?

239
00:23:01,320 --> 00:23:04,100
那里离机场一个半小时路程  鲍勃
But we're an hour and a half from an airport, Bob.

240
00:23:04,950 --> 00:23:06,600
太远了
It's too remote for...

241
00:23:11,540 --> 00:23:14,070
他们不是要接手度假村
Okay, they're not taking over a resort.

242
00:23:15,500 --> 00:23:17,210
他们要建机场
They're building an airport.

243
00:23:17,210 --> 00:23:19,420
但他们没有理由建机场啊
But there's no reason to build an airport

244
00:23:19,420 --> 00:23:21,240
那里根本没有滑雪场
because there is no ski resort.

245
00:23:29,270 --> 00:23:31,810
你在内政部认识谁
Who do you know at the Department of the Interior?

246
00:23:31,810 --> 00:23:33,390
我认识内政部长
I know the Secretary of the Interior.

247
00:23:33,400 --> 00:23:36,460
打给他  看看市场股票有没有租赁权
Call him. Find out if they gave them a lease.

248
00:23:38,610 --> 00:23:43,640
他们要建机场和滑雪场
They are building an airport and a ski resort...

249
00:23:45,320 --> 00:23:47,660
然后在周围建立一座新城市
And then they're gonna build a city around it.

250
00:23:47,660 --> 00:23:50,310
周围的地能买多少买多少  贝丝
Buy everything you can around them, Beth.

251
00:23:50,540 --> 00:23:51,170
全买了
Everything.

252
00:23:51,170 --> 00:23:53,900
他们怎么知道这个地方的
How the fuck did they know about this place?

253
00:23:55,830 --> 00:23:57,790
大通银行在管理他们的资金吗
I mean, does Chase manage their funds?

254
00:23:57,790 --> 00:23:58,790
应该是高盛集团
Goldman, I think.

255
00:23:58,800 --> 00:23:59,740
好吧
All right.

256
00:24:01,130 --> 00:24:04,200
谁是那里对冲基金的大佬
Who's the big, swinging dick in hedge funds over there?

257
00:24:04,300 --> 00:24:06,300
高盛集团的热门对冲基金是谁在管理
Who runs the hot hedge funds at Goldman?

258
00:24:06,300 --> 00:24:09,010
麦卡·格林伯格的基金  还有罗尔克·莫里斯
There's Micah Greenberg's fund, and Roarke Morris.

259
00:24:09,010 --> 00:24:10,220
他的基金非常火
His fund's on fire.

260
00:24:10,220 --> 00:24:11,970
谁的主营房地产
All right, who's heavy in real estate?

261
00:24:11,980 --> 00:24:12,850
罗尔克
Roarke.

262
00:24:12,850 --> 00:24:15,310
他运作度假村的过桥贷款
He bridges lines of credit on resort properties

263
00:24:15,310 --> 00:24:16,810
然后卖给他的基金
then sells them to his fund.

264
00:24:16,810 --> 00:24:17,980
骗局
Fucking shell game.

265
00:24:17,980 --> 00:24:19,630
他的名字叫什么
All right, what's his first name?

266
00:24:19,820 --> 00:24:20,520
罗尔克
Roarke.

267
00:24:20,530 --> 00:24:21,970
这是他的名字吗
That's his first name?

268
00:24:21,990 --> 00:24:23,640
这就不是名字
Not a fucking first name.

269
00:24:26,870 --> 00:24:28,800
{\an8}罗尔克·莫里斯

270
00:24:31,160 --> 00:24:33,020
逗我呢
You've got to be fucking kidding me.

271
00:24:33,710 --> 00:24:34,940
你认识他吗
You know him?

272
00:24:35,710 --> 00:24:38,670
很像露西尔·鲍尔和法比奥生的孩子
Um, it's like Lucille Ball and Fabio had a kid

273
00:24:38,670 --> 00:24:41,490
而我得去和他做个交易
and I have to go make a fucking deal with him.

274
00:24:41,550 --> 00:24:43,780
该死
Goddamn it.

275
00:24:44,470 --> 00:24:46,580
苏珊  帮我找找
Uh, Susan, would you, uh...

276
00:24:47,010 --> 00:24:50,370
十字溪农场的地址  谢谢
Get me the address for Cross Creek Ranch, please.

277
00:24:50,680 --> 00:24:51,680
马上
Coming your way.

278
00:24:51,680 --> 00:24:55,100
我先和那个傻逼谈谈  看他们有什么计划
Let me go talk to dip-fuck first, see what their plans are.

279
00:24:55,100 --> 00:24:56,250
回聊
Call you later.

280
00:25:18,790 --> 00:25:20,490
股票市场
Market Equities.

281
00:25:21,590 --> 00:25:22,900
舒瓦茨和梅耶
Schwartz and Meyer.

282
00:25:23,800 --> 00:25:25,050
你是鲍勃·施瓦茨的女人
You're Bob Schwartz's girl.

283
00:25:25,050 --> 00:25:26,320
我不是任何人的女人
I'm nobody's girl.

284
00:25:26,800 --> 00:25:28,090
反正是某人的女人
You're somebody's girl.

285
00:25:28,090 --> 00:25:31,910
先别唱比利·乔的歌了  好吗
Okay, let's stop speaking in Billy Joel songs for starters, okay?

286
00:25:32,100 --> 00:25:33,140
运动俱乐部
The Sporting Club.

287
00:25:33,140 --> 00:25:34,560
-杰克逊·布朗  -什么
- Jackson Browne. - What?

288
00:25:34,560 --> 00:25:36,170
《某人的女人》是杰克逊·布朗唱的
"Somebody's Girl" is Jackson Browne.

289
00:25:36,180 --> 00:25:38,960
好吧  我的错  你个混蛋
Okay, my mistake, you fucking cheese dick.

290
00:25:39,440 --> 00:25:41,560
-运动俱乐部  -怎么了
- The Sporting Club. - Yeah?

291
00:25:41,570 --> 00:25:43,050
很适合建机场
Good place for an airport.

292
00:25:43,360 --> 00:25:44,300
是的
It is.

293
00:25:44,360 --> 00:25:45,480
什么样的机场
What kind of airport?

294
00:25:45,490 --> 00:25:48,100
你和你兄弟用的私人机场吗
Is it the kind of airport for you and your buddies' Gulfstreams?

295
00:25:48,410 --> 00:25:49,930
更大一点
Thinking a little bigger than that.

296
00:25:50,820 --> 00:25:52,020
大多少
How much bigger?

297
00:25:52,950 --> 00:25:54,890
两个航站楼  52个闸口
Two terminals. Fifty-two gates.

298
00:25:55,200 --> 00:25:56,600
为什么选这里
Why here?

299
00:25:57,250 --> 00:25:59,230
首先  这里没什么风
Wind. For one. There isn't much.

300
00:25:59,710 --> 00:26:02,150
我想建在利文斯顿东北部  但是
Could build northeast of Livingston, but ...

301
00:26:02,590 --> 00:26:03,990
风太大了
Too much wind.

302
00:26:05,090 --> 00:26:07,550
说实话吧  没人喜欢下了飞机
And let's be honest, people don't want to fly,

303
00:26:07,550 --> 00:26:09,620
再开一个小时车去滑雪
then drive another hour to ski.

304
00:26:10,050 --> 00:26:11,800
这就是大天空滑雪场不火的原因
It's why Big Sky never took off.

305
00:26:11,800 --> 00:26:13,010
那里有美国最大的山
It's the largest mountain in America.

306
00:26:13,010 --> 00:26:16,460
西半球最好的雪  可是没人去滑雪
The best snow in this hemisphere and the slopes are empty

307
00:26:16,890 --> 00:26:18,290
就是因为要开车
because of the drive.

308
00:26:20,400 --> 00:26:23,720
人们就是这么懒
People are just that goddamn lazy.

309
00:26:27,490 --> 00:26:29,530
你拿到林务局的租赁权了吗
Did you secure a forest service lease?

310
00:26:29,530 --> 00:26:30,930
我什么都没拿到
I didn't secure anything.

311
00:26:31,870 --> 00:26:34,060
我只是管理了一个他们投资的基金
I manage a fund that invests their capital.

312
00:26:34,700 --> 00:26:36,830
我是董事会成员  所以我知道发生的事
I sit on the board so I know what's happening,

313
00:26:36,830 --> 00:26:39,650
但我无法控制
but I don't control what's happening.

314
00:26:44,790 --> 00:26:46,320
而你们
You, on the other hand...

315
00:26:48,050 --> 00:26:51,370
民兵和赌场老板杀害竞争对手
Militias and casino owners killing their competition.

316
00:26:51,510 --> 00:26:54,080
太酷炫了
It's fucking fascinating.

317
00:26:54,100 --> 00:26:56,040
老西部  还是很狂野
The Old West. Still wild.

318
00:26:57,640 --> 00:26:58,630
以后不会了
Not anymore.

319
00:26:59,560 --> 00:27:00,960
我们来了以后就不会了
Not when we get here.

320
00:27:01,270 --> 00:27:02,840
这些破事到此为止了
All that shit stops.

321
00:27:03,310 --> 00:27:04,760
想得挺美啊
Think so, do you?

322
00:27:07,690 --> 00:27:09,430
假装你的家人不住在这里
Pretend your family doesn't live here.

323
00:27:09,740 --> 00:27:11,850
假装你对这个地方一无所知
Pretend you don't know anything about this place.

324
00:27:12,700 --> 00:27:14,560
你的最终目的是什么
What would your end game be?

325
00:27:18,700 --> 00:27:20,560
我会打造一个公园城
I'd turn it into Park City.

326
00:27:20,910 --> 00:27:23,210
这才对嘛  丹·詹金斯是个聪明人
Now you're talking. Dan Jenkins was a smart guy.

327
00:27:23,210 --> 00:27:26,610
但他的梦想还不够大
But his dreams just weren't big enough.

328
00:27:27,250 --> 00:27:28,710
既然能建城市
Why dream about building golf courses

329
00:27:28,710 --> 00:27:30,530
还建什么高尔夫球场
when you can build cities?

330
00:27:31,880 --> 00:27:35,370
而你  你家是山谷最大的地主
And you, your family's the largest landowner in the valley,

331
00:27:35,930 --> 00:27:38,470
你让舒瓦茨和梅耶公成为了第二大地主
you've made Schwartz and Meyer the second largest.

332
00:27:38,470 --> 00:27:40,270
别跟我装无辜
Don't play babe in the woods with me.

333
00:27:40,270 --> 00:27:42,250
你从盐湖城就开始从事猎头了
You've been head-hunting since Salt Lake.

334
00:27:43,560 --> 00:27:46,730
我觉得这样问很可笑  但我很好奇
I feel ridiculous asking this, but I'm just so curious about

335
00:27:46,730 --> 00:27:48,900
你的猪脑子是怎么长的
how your pickled mind works:

336
00:27:48,900 --> 00:27:52,680
你考虑过住在这里的农场主吗
have you given any thought at all to the ranchers who live here?

337
00:27:53,450 --> 00:27:55,180
他们怎么办
And what'll happen to them?

338
00:27:55,370 --> 00:27:56,640
他们怎么办
What'll happen to them?

339
00:27:56,910 --> 00:27:58,200
他们不用再当农场主了
They won't have to be ranchers anymore

340
00:27:58,200 --> 00:28:00,520
因为他们都发财了
because they're all so fucking rich.

341
00:28:03,160 --> 00:28:04,270
回答得漂亮
Good answer.

342
00:28:12,260 --> 00:28:13,670
我爸告诉过我
My dad told me once:

343
00:28:13,680 --> 00:28:14,990
总有一天
there will come a day

344
00:28:15,550 --> 00:28:17,830
唯一尊贵的工作就是钓鱼
when the only noble job left is fishing

345
00:28:18,100 --> 00:28:20,420
因为没人能找到拥有海洋的方法
because no one's figured out a way to own the ocean.

346
00:28:21,600 --> 00:28:23,210
-这也是暂时的  -没错
- Yet. - That's right.

347
00:28:23,390 --> 00:28:24,590
我正在想办法
I'm working on it.

348
00:28:26,350 --> 00:28:27,590
可不嘛
I bet you are.

349
00:28:32,860 --> 00:28:34,430
走的时候  小心别轧到花
Mind the flowers when you leave.

350
00:28:34,820 --> 00:28:35,930
好的
Will do.

351
00:29:02,890 --> 00:29:04,290
这妹子我喜欢
I like this girl.

352
00:29:10,780 --> 00:29:19,020
{\an8}黄石
达顿农场

353
00:30:07,130 --> 00:30:08,300
西班牙人吗
That Spanish?

354
00:30:08,300 --> 00:30:09,510
我也不知道
I don't know.

355
00:30:09,510 --> 00:30:12,160
不过我告诉你  她挺给力的
I'll tell you one thing, though: she's a hand.

356
00:30:13,180 --> 00:30:15,470
技术肯定没问题
Ride the hair off a horse, that's for damn sure.

357
00:30:15,470 --> 00:30:18,120
但我们需要一个会说英语的人
But we need someone who can speak English.

358
00:30:25,820 --> 00:30:27,220
你在哪学的牛仔
Where'd you learn to cowboy?

359
00:30:31,450 --> 00:30:33,220
不是西班牙语  是得州话
That's ain't Spanish. That's Texan.

360
00:30:33,780 --> 00:30:36,030
这哪是得州话  她在胡扯
That's ain't Texan. That's gibberish.

361
00:30:36,030 --> 00:30:37,410
不  她肯定是得州人
No, I'm telling you, it's Texan.

362
00:30:37,410 --> 00:30:39,480
我一英里外就能闻出来  你叫什么名字
I can smell 'em a mile away. What's your name?

363
00:30:39,580 --> 00:30:40,610
泰特
Teeter.

364
00:30:41,710 --> 00:30:42,610
什么
What's that?

365
00:30:44,080 --> 00:30:45,650
泰  特
Tee-ter.

366
00:30:46,880 --> 00:30:49,030
你听懂了吗  她好像说的是"彼得"
Did you hear that? I think she's saying "Peter".

367
00:30:49,090 --> 00:30:50,300
你叫彼得吗
Your name Peter?

368
00:30:50,300 --> 00:30:52,680
我看起来像叫彼得吗
Do I look like my fucking name is Peter,

369
00:30:52,680 --> 00:30:54,680
你个臭傻逼
you skunk-hard motherfucker?

370
00:30:54,680 --> 00:30:56,680
她刚刚说我是傻逼
She just called me a motherfucker.

371
00:30:56,680 --> 00:30:58,010
你应该听得懂吧
You understood, that, didn't you,

372
00:30:58,010 --> 00:30:59,850
你个罗圈腿傻屌
you bow-legged bastard.

373
00:30:59,850 --> 00:31:02,980
你看起来就像躺在什么医疗装置上
Hey, you look like you all got bent over on one of them nurse things,

374
00:31:02,980 --> 00:31:05,400
被操着屁眼  操的膝盖都弯了
fucked up the ass 'til your knees buckled.

375
00:31:05,400 --> 00:31:07,980
这种女孩送去高中
This is the kind of girl that got drove to high school

376
00:31:07,980 --> 00:31:09,650
都得戴冰球头盔的
wearing a damn hockey helmet.

377
00:31:09,650 --> 00:31:12,610
她会像野火一样烧穿工棚的
She's gonna go through the bunkhouse like wildfire.

378
00:31:12,610 --> 00:31:15,640
她很完美  相信我  雇她吧
She's perfect. Trust me. Hire her.

379
00:31:19,240 --> 00:31:20,330
什么情况
What is this?

380
00:31:20,330 --> 00:31:21,900
小小的招聘会
A little job fair.

381
00:31:22,290 --> 00:31:24,070
现在开始雇女牛仔了吗
Hiring cowgirls now?

382
00:31:24,460 --> 00:31:26,540
黄石的男女机会平等
We're equal opportunity here at Yellowstone.

383
00:31:26,540 --> 00:31:29,700
再说了  女人干得多  吃得少
Plus, women work twice as hard and eat half as much.

384
00:31:29,960 --> 00:31:32,120
你真是太有才了  你知道吗
You're a real renaissance man, you know that?

385
00:31:32,260 --> 00:31:33,700
低调  低调
Don't tell anybody, now.

386
00:31:40,140 --> 00:31:41,270
看到我父亲了吗
Seen my father?

387
00:31:41,270 --> 00:31:42,600
嗯  他去夏季营地了
Yeah, he's up at summer camp.

388
00:31:42,600 --> 00:31:43,670
其他人都去了
With everyone else.

389
00:31:45,190 --> 00:31:46,960
他不接电话
He's not answering his phone.

390
00:31:47,400 --> 00:31:48,880
他故意的
Well, that's by design.

391
00:31:51,030 --> 00:31:51,970
出什么事了吗
Something wrong?

392
00:31:53,110 --> 00:31:54,530
我可以给他捎个口信
I can get a message to him if you want.

393
00:31:54,530 --> 00:31:56,060
没事
Nothing's wrong.

394
00:31:57,160 --> 00:31:58,730
只是人生
It's just life.

395
00:31:58,740 --> 00:32:00,310
一直在变
Always changing.

396
00:32:01,080 --> 00:32:03,150
这是他唯一不愿意看到的
The one thing he doesn't want it to do.

397
00:32:04,460 --> 00:32:05,650
回头见
See you soon.

398
00:32:05,960 --> 00:32:06,820
也许吧
Maybe.

399
00:32:07,330 --> 00:32:10,280
我们已经过了"欲擒故纵"的年纪了吧  贝丝
We're well past playing "hard to get", don't you think, Beth?

400
00:32:11,760 --> 00:32:12,820
你和我
You and me,

401
00:32:14,050 --> 00:32:16,160
"欲擒故纵"永远也玩不腻  宝贝
we're never past playing "hard to get", baby.

402
00:32:45,330 --> 00:32:48,000
{\an8}急救护理

403
00:32:48,120 --> 00:32:49,610
看清是谁干的了吗
You get a good look at who did it?

404
00:32:50,090 --> 00:32:51,110
嗯
Yeah.

405
00:32:51,920 --> 00:32:53,990
看清了  就是那些混蛋
Yeah, it was those sons of bitches over there.

406
00:32:54,670 --> 00:32:55,670
你把他们关在哪里
Where you holding 'em?

407
00:32:55,670 --> 00:32:57,990
几个骑牛者看到他们上了她的车
Couple bull riders saw 'em getting in her truck.

408
00:32:58,590 --> 00:33:00,330
拦住了他们  替我们拖住了他们
Tackled 'em and held 'em for us.

409
00:33:00,550 --> 00:33:02,160
-他们在马厩  -好
- They're in the horse stall. - Okay.

410
00:33:09,480 --> 00:33:11,260
这些混蛋得吸取一点教训
These fuckers need to learn a lesson.

411
00:33:11,820 --> 00:33:14,800
治治他们  让他们跟县监狱的罪犯都讲讲
Something they'll tell every criminal in county jail who'll listen.

412
00:33:16,650 --> 00:33:17,890
你有什么主意吗
You got any ideas?

413
00:33:21,120 --> 00:33:23,180
在这里不行  人太多了
Can't do it here. There's too many people.

414
00:33:25,410 --> 00:33:26,410
我有个主意
I got an idea.

415
00:33:26,410 --> 00:33:27,650
-是吗  -嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.

416
00:33:31,840 --> 00:33:32,780
女士
Ma'am.

417
00:33:33,340 --> 00:33:34,360
打扰一下  女士
Excuse me, ma'am?

418
00:33:35,050 --> 00:33:37,780
我能看看你的卡车和拖车有什么损失吗
Do you mind if I see if they did any damage to your truck and trailer?

419
00:33:38,130 --> 00:33:39,030
当然
Sure.

420
00:33:39,050 --> 00:33:40,030
能把钥匙给我吗
May I see your keys?

421
00:33:43,760 --> 00:33:45,080
很好  哪辆
Great, which rig is it?

422
00:33:45,100 --> 00:33:47,290
黑色卡车的那辆
It's the black one with the black truck.

423
00:33:47,680 --> 00:33:48,580
好的
Okay.

424
00:33:50,730 --> 00:33:52,710
我摆平那些混蛋
I'm gonna take care of those pieces of shit.

425
00:33:52,730 --> 00:33:53,810
在拖车等我
I want you to meet me at the trailer.

426
00:33:53,820 --> 00:33:55,520
别说出去  好吗
Keep the zips on, okay?

427
00:33:55,530 --> 00:33:56,760
-知道了  -去吧
- Got it. - Go.

428
00:34:38,490 --> 00:34:40,010
看这里  混蛋
Look up here, assholes.

429
00:34:41,820 --> 00:34:44,100
你们的行为应该被绞死
I oughta hang you for what you did.

430
00:34:46,490 --> 00:34:48,980
但如果你们愿意  我也可以给你们上一课
But this could be a teaching moment if you let it.

431
00:35:46,010 --> 00:35:47,160
疼吗
Does it hurt?

432
00:36:04,570 --> 00:36:05,550
混蛋
Fucker!

433
00:36:33,430 --> 00:36:34,880
他们应该吸取教训了
I think they learned their lesson.

434
00:36:36,060 --> 00:36:38,340
很好  把这些混蛋送监狱吧
Good. Let's take these assholes to jail.

435
00:36:42,730 --> 00:36:43,880
好了  小子们
All right, boys.

436
00:36:51,580 --> 00:36:53,270
我操
Holy shit.

437
00:36:53,790 --> 00:36:55,190
你都干了什么
What the hell did you do?

438
00:38:14,500 --> 00:38:16,440
没完没了
Always fucking something.

439
00:39:04,510 --> 00:39:06,740
你在干什么
What in the fuck are you doing now?

440
00:39:07,680 --> 00:39:13,080
35年来  我从未独自待在这个农场过
In 35 years, I've have never been alone on this ranch.

441
00:39:16,690 --> 00:39:18,340
现在没人了  里普
And we're all alone, Rip.

442
00:39:23,570 --> 00:39:25,400
我们想做什么都行
We can do whatever we want.

443
00:39:25,410 --> 00:39:27,030
宝贝  你一直在做你想做的事
Baby, you've been doing whatever you want

444
00:39:27,030 --> 00:39:27,990
你的一生都在做
your whole damn life.

445
00:39:27,990 --> 00:39:29,530
但没人能看见我们
But no one can see us.

446
00:39:29,530 --> 00:39:31,440
我们可以脱光
We could take off all our clothes

447
00:39:32,250 --> 00:39:34,730
在农场裸奔
and we could go running naked through the field,

448
00:39:35,080 --> 00:39:36,540
没人会知道的
and no one will know about it.

449
00:39:36,540 --> 00:39:37,460
这样吧
I'll tell you what,

450
00:39:37,460 --> 00:39:39,210
你去农场裸奔
why don't you run butt-ass naked through that field,

451
00:39:39,210 --> 00:39:40,840
我穿着牛仔裤坐在这里  看着你
and I'll sit here in my jeans and I'll watch you do it,

452
00:39:40,840 --> 00:39:41,860
你觉得怎么样
what do you say?

453
00:39:42,510 --> 00:39:45,530
你有什么想做却没做的事
Is there anything you ever wanted to do that you didn't do

454
00:39:46,260 --> 00:39:48,550
因为所有人会盯着你  质问你
because everybody would watch you and question you

455
00:39:48,550 --> 00:39:51,100
现在可以不管他们
and now doing it is in spite of them

456
00:39:51,100 --> 00:39:53,180
而是因为别的
and it's about something else

457
00:39:53,180 --> 00:39:55,430
你想象的那一刻
and the moment you imagined is not

458
00:39:55,440 --> 00:39:57,210
并不是你活着的那一刻
the moment that you were living?

459
00:39:58,150 --> 00:39:59,670
你明白吗
Does that make sense to you?

460
00:40:01,730 --> 00:40:04,930
说实话  我完全没听懂
Honestly, I don't even know what you just said.

461
00:40:08,910 --> 00:40:10,070
我想做一件事
You know, there is something I want to do.

462
00:40:10,070 --> 00:40:12,230
留在这里
Just, uh, just stay here.

463
00:40:13,950 --> 00:40:15,560
有意思
This sounds interesting.

464
00:40:33,430 --> 00:40:35,520
我们要在土里干  是吗
We're fucking in the dirt, aren't we?

465
00:40:35,520 --> 00:40:37,290
稍微沾点土吧
Maybe in a little bit.

466
00:40:47,110 --> 00:40:48,430
但我们先跳支舞吧
But first we're gonna dance.

467
00:41:41,000 --> 00:41:42,530
还有饼干吗
Any more biscuits?

468
00:41:43,880 --> 00:41:45,950
应该还有很多
Yeah, well, I think there's plenty.

469
00:41:48,380 --> 00:41:49,280
给
There you go.

470
00:41:50,760 --> 00:41:52,410
这点可不够
I'm gonna need more than that.

471
00:41:53,430 --> 00:41:54,370
好吧
All right.

472
00:41:56,560 --> 00:41:57,620
再来一个
Another one.

473
00:41:59,930 --> 00:42:02,500
你和你父亲一样
You're just... You're just like your father.

474
00:42:07,320 --> 00:42:08,720
你知道我妻子
You know my wife...

475
00:42:10,110 --> 00:42:12,760
她以前会烤满满两个荷兰锅的饼干
she used to make two Dutch ovens full of biscuits:

476
00:42:12,780 --> 00:42:16,350
一锅给你爸  一锅给我们
one for your father and one for the rest of us.

477
00:42:17,410 --> 00:42:21,110
他会站在火堆旁问他妈妈"还要多久"
He'd stand right by the fire and ask his mother, "How long?".

478
00:42:21,580 --> 00:42:25,070
然后她说"五分钟"
And she'd say, "Five more minutes".

479
00:42:25,670 --> 00:42:27,380
这对我妻子来说只是"很快"的意思
Which just meant "soon" to my wife.

480
00:42:27,380 --> 00:42:28,880
并不代表真的是五分钟
It didn't mean five minutes.

481
00:42:28,880 --> 00:42:30,700
有时也不止半小时
Didn't mean thirty minutes sometimes...

482
00:42:32,300 --> 00:42:35,040
他会跺脚撅嘴
He'd stomp off and pout

483
00:42:35,850 --> 00:42:37,890
然后走开  回来再问一次
and walk away and come back and ask again

484
00:42:37,890 --> 00:42:39,750
这个对话能持续一个小时
and that shit would go on for an hour...

485
00:42:42,140 --> 00:42:43,390
饼干终于烤好以后
And when they were finally ready,

486
00:42:43,390 --> 00:42:45,060
他就只拿一盘饼干
he'd take a plate of biscuits, nothing else,

487
00:42:45,060 --> 00:42:47,110
坐在火光边
and he'd just go sit at the edge of the firelight

488
00:42:47,110 --> 00:42:50,180
背对着我们  双手并用  狼吞虎咽的
with his back to us and he'd just go at it with both his hands.

489
00:42:50,490 --> 00:42:51,590
真的很好吃
They were really good.

490
00:42:53,570 --> 00:42:54,950
有什么好笑的  真的很好吃嘛
Why is that funny? They were really good.

491
00:42:54,950 --> 00:42:56,600
像野狗一样
Like a wild dog.

492
00:42:59,370 --> 00:43:01,700
在荷兰锅旁站了一个小时后
After an hour of standing over that Dutch oven,

493
00:43:01,700 --> 00:43:03,520
她会坐在我旁边
she'd sit beside me,

494
00:43:05,120 --> 00:43:07,320
头发乱糟糟的  一股烟味
her hair a mess, smelling like smoke,

495
00:43:08,290 --> 00:43:12,030
她压根不喜欢烤饼干  所以非常生气
madder than hell because she hated cooking those damn biscuits.

496
00:43:12,630 --> 00:43:14,200
我看着她说
And I looked at her and said,

497
00:43:15,380 --> 00:43:17,430
"亲爱的  你给他什么他都吃
"Sweetheart, he'll eat anything you put in front of him.

498
00:43:17,430 --> 00:43:21,500
给他做点不用花这么长时间的东西呗"
Just make him something else that doesn't take all night."

499
00:43:24,100 --> 00:43:26,500
你妈妈看着我说"我知道
Your mom looked at me and she said: "I know.

500
00:43:29,190 --> 00:43:31,930
但如果我不做  我真的没办法看着他吃"
But if I don't make 'em I can't watch him eat them."

501
00:43:36,780 --> 00:43:38,520
然后她进了帐篷
Then she went to the tent,

502
00:43:39,870 --> 00:43:41,730
躺下睡着了
laid down and fell asleep.

503
00:43:44,460 --> 00:43:46,980
我们要打烙印  所以我比她先起
We were branding so I was up before her.

504
00:43:52,420 --> 00:43:54,870
那是她对我说的最后一句话
That was the last thing she ever said to me.

505
00:44:01,640 --> 00:44:04,460
在她的生日  我还在给牛打上烙印
Branding cattle on her goddamn birthday.

506
00:44:39,640 --> 00:44:41,660
让人不禁好奇这一切的意义
Makes you wonder the point of it all.

507
00:44:43,640 --> 00:44:47,290
找到深爱的人  然后失去他们
Find someone you love so much just to lose them.

508
00:44:50,690 --> 00:44:53,380
我也希望相信这是上帝的安排  但我
I'd like to believe there's a plan to it all, but I...

509
00:44:55,530 --> 00:44:57,090
我看不到
I don't see a plan.

510
00:45:00,950 --> 00:45:03,020
因为我们就在其中  爸
That's just 'cause we're inside it, Dad.

511
00:45:05,660 --> 00:45:06,900
我们看到安排了
We see the plan.

512
00:45:08,920 --> 00:45:10,190
我们正站在上面
We're standing on it.

513
00:45:13,340 --> 00:45:17,160
是吧  可能吧
Yeah. Guess we are.

514
00:45:37,650 --> 00:45:40,610
这是来自甜草谷监狱的付费电话
This is a collect call from the Sweet Grass Valley jail.

515
00:45:40,610 --> 00:45:43,310
请按1接听电话
Please press one to accept this call.

516
00:45:47,580 --> 00:45:49,270
达顿委员  长官
Comm... Commissioner Dutton, sir?

517
00:45:49,290 --> 00:45:51,110
亨顿探员
Agent Hendon?

518
00:45:53,460 --> 00:45:54,780
没事吧
Is everything okay?

519
00:45:56,750 --> 00:45:59,160
长官  出事了
Um, no, sir, it's not.

520
00:46:01,630 --> 00:46:03,910
我有
I, um... I've got a...

521
00:46:06,560 --> 00:46:08,250
长官  我们有麻烦了
Sir, we have a problem.

522
00:46:16,400 --> 00:46:18,220
达顿委员  长官
Commissioner Dutton, sir?

